Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files A-E, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files B
    - BeShears, Bill (Box A-11, Folder 199)
    - Bess, John (Box A-11, Folder 200)
      One print has caption affixed to verso.
    - Bess, Julia D. (Box A-11, Folder 201)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo
    - Bess, Lorna (Box A-11, Folder 202)
    - BEST (Basic Essential Skills Training) (Box A-11, Folder 203)
      Three prints have captions glued to verso. Also includes press release.
    - Best, Alvin (Box A-11, Folder 204)
    - Best, Cynthia (Box A-11, Folder 205)
    - Best, Edward (Box A-11, Folder 206)
      Photographer if identified: Publicity Photographers
    - Best, George M. (P.+L.) (Box A-11, Folder 207)
    - Best, Jay (Box A-11, Folder 208)
    - Best, Leroy (Box A-11, Folder 209)
      Print has typescript leaf attached with paperclip.
    - Best, Lincoln (Dr.) (Box A-11, Folder 210)
      Photographer if identified: Rothschild Photo
    - Best, Margaret (Mrs.) (Box A-11, Folder 211)
    - Best, Richard A. (Box A-11, Folder 212)
    - Best, Skeeter (Clifton) (Box A-11, Folder 213)
    - Best, Vincent E. (Box A-11, Folder 214)
    - Best, William (Box A-11, Folder 215)
      Photographer if identified: Al Burley, Harris Photo, James Gilbert, Bro. David McAdams
    - Betancourt, Ismael (Box A-11, Folder 216)
    - Betha, John H. (Rev.) (Box A-11, Folder 217)
    - Bethany Baptist Church (Box A-11, Folder 218)
      One print has two typescript leaves attached with paperclip. Another has a staple in it.
      Photographer if identified: Ace Creative Photos, Archie "Lynum" Smitherman, Rufus Merritt, Harris Photo
    - Bethany Church (Box A-11, Folder 219)
      One print has caption taped to recto and ms. leaf attached with paperclip. Also contains one typescript leaf.
      Photographer if identified: Van Picture ServiceInc.
    - Bethea, Alexander (Box A-11, Folder 220)
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen Photography
    - Bethea, Clyde (Box A-11, Folder 221)
    - Bethea, Jeanette (Box A-11, Folder 222)
    - Bethea, Juanita (Box A-11, Folder 223)
    - Bethea, Randy (Box A-11, Folder 224)
    - Bethel, Baltron B. (Box A-11, Folder 225)
    - Bethel, Ernestine (Box A-11, Folder 226)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Hayes Photography
    - Bethel Gospel Tabernacle (Box A-11, Folder 227)
    - Bethel, Pepsi (Box A-11, Folder 228)
    - Bethel Tabenacle A.M.B. Church (Box A-11, Folder 229)
    - Bethel Temple Church (Box A-11, Folder 230)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Carter, A. Hansen Studio
    - Bethesda Baptist Church (Box A-11, Folder 231)
    - Bethune Cookman College (Box A-11, Folder 232)
      One print has press release stapled to recto. Five prints are mounted to cardboard and attached at the sides. Two prints are attached to a press release with paperclips. Also one velox print.
    - Bethune, Mary McLeod (Box A-11, Folder 233)
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen Studio, Arnold C. DeMille, David J. M. Robinson, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Bethune, Teresa (Box A-11, Folder 234)
    - Bethune Towers (Box A-11, Folder 235)
    - Bettis, Gladys A. (Box A-11, Folder 236)
    - Bettis, Rachel (Box A-11, Folder 237)
      Blank leaf pasted to verso.
    - Betts, Ann (Box A-11, Folder 238)
    - Bevel, James L. (Rev.) (Box A-11, Folder 239)
    - Bevel, James (Rev.) (Box A-11, Folder 240)
    - Beverly, Anthony (Box A-11, Folder 241)
    - Beverly, Clarence (Dr.) (Box A-11, Folder 242)
    - Beverly, Clarence (Dr. + Mrs.) (Box A-11, Folder 243)
    - Beverly, Frankie (Box A-11, Folder 244)
    - Beverly, Harold + daughter Carol (Box A-11, Folder 245)
    - Beverly, Trazana (Box A-11, Folder 246)
    - Bevins, Grace R. (Mrs.) (Box A-11, Folder 247)
    - Bey, Andy (Box A-11, Folder 248)
    - Bey, Ben (Box A-11, Folder 249)
    - Bey, Gloria Jones (Box A-11, Folder 250)
    - Bey, James (Box A-11, Folder 251)
    - Bey, Jane (Mrs.) (Box A-11, Folder 252)
    - Bey, La Rocque (Box A-11, Folder 253)
      One print has two ms. leaves stapled to verso. Another print has caption glued to verso. Two other prints have caption taped to verso. Also includes two typescript leaves and one business card.
      Photographer if identified: Monroe S. Frederick II, Harris Photo, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Big M Photo Service, A. Hansen Photography
    - Bey, La Rocque (Box A-11, Folder 254)
      One print has caption attached with paperclip. Also contains one press release.
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen Photography, Harris Photo, Norman Frederick, Pictorial Enterprise, Greene Photo
    - Bey, Michelle Habersham (Box A-11, Folder 255)
    - Bey, Salome (Box A-11, Folder 256)
    - Bhekuzula, Zwelithini Goodwill Kacurian (King) (Box A-11, Folder 257)
    - Biafran Dancers (Box A-11, Folder 258)
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen Photography, David McAdams
    - Biafrans (Box A-11, Folder 259)
    - Biaggi, Mario (Box A-11, Folder 260)
      One print has caption glued to verso. Another print has caption taped to verso. Also contains four velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: Grand Photographers, Harris Photo, Frank Parlatore
    - Bibb, Leon (Box A-11, Folder 261)
      Five prints have caption glued to verso. One print has two typescript leaves attached with paperclip. Also contains typescript leaf and campaign poster for Lindsay.
      Photographer if identified: Friedman-Abeles, RCA Records, Ed Sullivan
    - Bibbs, Raymond (Box A-11, Folder 262)
    - Bibby, Henry (Box A-11, Folder 263)
    - Bible Way Worldwide Church (Box A-11, Folder 264)
      Two typescript leaves attached to print with paperclip and one typescript leaf glued to verso.
    - Biblo, Robert L. (Box A-11, Folder 265)
    - Bicycles (Box A-11, Folder 266)
      Also one velox print. One print has staple in it.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Coreen Simpson, Kwame Brathwaite, Bob Head
    - Biddy Basketball League (Box A-12, Folder 1)
      Photographer if identified: Bro. David McAdams, Robert W. Cottrol,
    - Biden, Sen. Joseph (Box A-12, Folder 2)
    - The Big Apple Sickle Cell Camp Fund (Box A-12, Folder 3)
      Press release stapled to verso of print.
      Photographer if identified: Bruce Williams
    - Big Bird (Box A-12, Folder 4)
    - Big Brothers (Box A-12, Folder 5)
      9 prints are stuck together with paste. Press release taped to recto of one print.
    - Big Donald (Box A-12, Folder 6)
      Ms. leaf stapled to recto of print
    - "Bigfoot" (Box A-12, Folder 7)
    - Biggart, Henry (Box A-12, Folder 8)
    - Biggart, Henry D. (Box A-12, Folder 9)
    - Big Maybelle (see Inactive File) (Box A-12, Folder 10)
    - "Big Miller" (Box A-12, Folder 11)
    - Big Show (Box A-12, Folder 12)
    - Big Time Buck White (Box A-12, Folder 13)
    - Big Time Sarah (Box A-12, Folder 14)
    - Biggs, Eileen (Box A-12, Folder 15)
    - Biggs, Enrique Mrs. (Box A-12, Folder 16)
      Photographer if identified: Ted ProskinInc.
    - Biggs, Ernest (Box A-12, Folder 17)
    - Biggs, Herman Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-12, Folder 18)
    - Biggs, Larry (Box A-12, Folder 19)
    - Biggs, Lawrence G. (Box A-12, Folder 20)
    - Biggs, Verion (Box A-12, Folder 21)
    - Biggs, Verion (Box A-12, Folder 22)
    - Biko, Steve (Box A-12, Folder 23)
      Print is from the film Cry Freedom. Staple through edge of print.
    - Bilbuld, Elaine (Box A-12, Folder 24)
    - Bill and Marge (Box A-12, Folder 25)
    - Bellamy, Ralph (Box A-12, Folder 26)
    - Billings, Charles E. Dr. (Box A-12, Folder 27)
    - Billings, David J. (Box A-12, Folder 28)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Public Information Office, Parks Administration, Dick De Marsico, Joe Williams
    - Billings, Janie Mrs. (Box A-12, Folder 29)
    - Billingslea, Rebecka (Box A-12, Folder 30)
    - Billingsley, Andrew Dr. (Box A-12, Folder 31)
    - Billingsley, Roy (Box A-12, Folder 32)
    - Billingsley, Stephanie (Box A-12, Folder 33)
    - Billops, Camille (Box A-12, Folder 34)
      Photographer if identified: Hatch-Billops Studio
    - Billups, Julius (Rev.) (Box A-12, Folder 35)
      Print has a typescript leaf attached by staple.
    - Billups, Lavely (Box A-12, Folder 36)
    - Billups, Rufus L. (Box A-12, Folder 37)
    - Bing, Dave (Box A-12, Folder 38)
    - Bing, Henry Jr. (Box A-12, Folder 39)
    - Bing, Rudolf (Box A-12, Folder 40)
      Staple through edge of print.
    - Bingham, Robert Dr. & Mrs. (Box A-12, Folder 41)
    - "Bingo Long Traveling All-Stars and Motor Kings" (Box A-12, Folder 42)
      promo stills from movie, and reproductions of Negro National League photographs.
    - Binns, Del Brook (Box A-12, Folder 43)
    - Binns, T. G. (Box A-12, Folder 44)
    - Birch, Willie (Box A-12, Folder 45)
    - Birchette, Mark (Box A-12, Folder 46)
    - Bird, Lester (Box A-12, Folder 47)
    - Bird, Vere C. (Box A-12, Folder 48)
    - Birds of Paradise (Box A-12, Folder 49)
      Staple through border of one print. Some prints are images of actual birds, others of an NAACP social club.
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen, Nichols
    - Birdsong, Cindy (Actress) (Box A-12, Folder 50)
    - Birdsong, Edwin (Box A-12, Folder 51)
    - Birkett, Rev. (Box A-12, Folder 52)
    - Birkett, Earl (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-12, Folder 53)
      Photographer if identified: M Associates, Empire Photographers,
    - Birkett, Lillian (Box A-12, Folder 54)
    - Birl, Jerry (Box A-12, Folder 55)
    - Birmingham, Alabama (bombing which killed 4 children) (Box A-12, Folder 56)
      Numerous press releases, WMCA radio broadcast texts and interview excerpts, and newspaper clippings from other New York newspapers' coverage of bombing.
    - Birmingham, Ala. (Box A-12, Folder 57)
      Photographer if identified: Elaine Tomlin
    - Birmingham Children's Rally Foley Square N.Y.C. Sept. 22, 1963) (Box A-12, Folder 58)
    - Birmingham, Frazier (Box A-12, Folder 59)
    - Birmingham, Mary (Box A-12, Folder 60)
    - Birth Control (Box A-12, Folder 61)
    - Birthday Celebrations (Box A-12, Folder 62)
      One print is a Polaroid. 2 prints have staples through border.
      Photographer if identified: Lem Peterkin, Pictorial Enterprise, Official Photograph President Borough of Queens, Bill Hayes, Austin Hansen, NYC Housing Authority, Lensman Photo
    - Donna Biscoe (Box A-12, Folder 63)
    - Bishop, Barbara H. (Box A-12, Folder 64)
    - Bishop, Clarence (Box A-12, Folder 65)
    - Bishop, Ed (Box A-12, Folder 66)
      Photographer if identified: Reggie Blackman, Dave Greene
    - Bishop, Hewlett R. (Box A-12, Folder 67)
    - Bishop, Jimmy (Box A-12, Folder 68)
    - Bishop, Marlene (Box A-12, Folder 69)
    - Bishop, Murray (Box A-12, Folder 70)
    - Bishop, Patricia (Box A-12, Folder 71)
      Both prints have staples through border.
      Photographer if identified: Will Weissberg
    - Bishop, Walter Jr. (Box A-12, Folder 72)
    - Bishop, William (Box A-12, Folder 73)
    - Bishop, Winnie (Box A-12, Folder 74)
    - Bishop College Choir (Box A-12, Folder 75)
    - Bispham, Eleanor Stephens (Box A-12, Folder 76)
    - Biss & Cosmic Funk (Box A-12, Folder 77)
    - Bivens, Diane E. (Box A-12, Folder 78)
    - Bivens, Charles (Box A-12, Folder 79)
      Photographer if identified: Tex Harris, Harris Photo
    - Bivens, Lena (Box A-12, Folder 80)
      Photographer if identified: Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise,
    - Bivens, Patricia (Box A-12, Folder 81)
    - Bivins, Charles (Box A-12, Folder 82)
    - Bivens, Edward Jr. (Box A-12, Folder 83)
    - Bizzel, Frank (Box A-12, Folder 84)
      Photographer if identified: M Associates, Bro. David McAdams, James Gilbert,
    - Blache, Joan A. (Box A-12, Folder 85)
    - Black Achievers (Box A-12, Folder 86)
      Also one typescript press release.
      Photographer if identified: Dave Greene Photo, Wagner International Photos, Willie Gorham, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Black, Al (Box A-12, Folder 87)
    - Black, Albert (Box A-12, Folder 88)
      Photographer if identified: Augusta Berns
    - Black Alumni (Box A-12, Folder 89)
      Photographer if identified: William L. Ballinger
    - Black American Racers (Box A-12, Folder 90)
    - Blacks & Jews (Box A-12, Folder 91)
    - Black Artists (Box A-12, Folder 92)
      Photographer if identified: Ruby Washington
    - "Black Athlete" film (Box A-12, Folder 93)
    - Black Bards (Box A-12, Folder 94)
    - Black Belt Jones (Box A-12, Folder 95)
      Movie stills.
    - Black, Bonita (Box A-12, Folder 96)
    - Black Bred (Box A-12, Folder 97)
    - Black Brewers (Box A-12, Folder 98)
    - Black Bull Fighter (Box A-12, Folder 99)
    - Blackburne, Laura (Box A-12, Folder 100)
    - Blackburn, Robert (Box A-12, Folder 101)
    - Black Businesses (Box A-12, Folder 102)
      Also 16 velox prints and several press releases.
    - Black Caesar (Box A-12, Folder 103)
    - Black Caucus (Box A-12, Folder 104)
      Also several press releases and one velox print of cutlines.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Frederick, United Press International, Official Photograph, The White House, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Black Caucus (Box A-12, Folder 105)
      Also one velox print, several press releases, newspaper clippings "for development," and press kit for Congressional Black Caucus 1973 dinner.
      Photographer if identified: United Press International, Wide World Photos, Aristocrat Studio of Photography, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Charles Sanders, Harris Photo
    - Black Caucus (Box A-12, Folder 106)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert,
    - Black, Chris (Bad Man) (Box A-12, Folder 107)
    - Black Citizens for a Fair Media (Box A-12, Folder 108)
    - Black, Cleveland (Box A-12, Folder 109)
    - Black, Cody (Box A-12, Folder 110)
    - Black College Day (Box A-12, Folder 111)
      Also print mechanicals.
      Photographer if identified: Charles Roland
    - Black Composers (Box A-12, Folder 112)
      Photographer if identified: Marbeth
    - Black Congressmen (Box A-12, Folder 113)
      Photographer if identified: Robert W. Cottrol
    - Black Convention (Box A-12, Folder 114)
      Photocopied newspaper clippings and press release.
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Juanita M. Cole
    - Black Correction Officers (Box A-12, Folder 115)
    - Black Designers (Box A-12, Folder 116)
    - Black Earth (Box A-12, Folder 117)
    - "Black Ecstasy" (Box A-12, Folder 118)
    - Black Encyclopedia of the Air (Box A-12, Folder 119)
    - Black Enterprise (Box A-12, Folder 120)
      Also one velox print and multiple press releases. 2 prints stapled together with press release on recto.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Bill Price, Dave Greene
    - Black Essence Dance Group (Box A-12, Folder 121)
    - Black, Ethel (Box A-12, Folder 122)
    - Black Experience Ensemble (Of Albany, N.Y.) (Box A-12, Folder 123)
    - Black Expo (Box A-12, Folder 124)
      Also multiple press releases.
      Photographer if identified: Gerald Peart, Harris Photo, Duke Sparks Applauds, Karl Crutchfield
    - Black Expression (Box A-12, Folder 125)
      Photographer if identified: P.G. Frankiin
    - Black Family (Box A-12, Folder 126)
    - Black Fashion Museum (Box A-12, Folder 127)
    - Black Filmmakers (Box A-12, Folder 128)
    - Black, Frederick H. (Box A-12, Folder 129)
    - Blackfrica (Box A-12, Folder 130)
    - Black Author's Forum (Box A-12, Folder 131)
      Photographer if identified: George Cohen
    - Black Girl (Box A-12, Folder 132)
    - Black Giants Sculptured Portraits (Box A-12, Folder 133)
    - Black, Gloria (Box A-12, Folder 134)
    - Black, Grace C. (Box A-12, Folder 135)
    - Black Hall Of Fame (Box A-12, Folder 136)
      Photographer if identified: Al Burley, Peter M. Lerman, Monroe S. Frederick III, J. Connaughton, Harris Photo,
    - Black Heat (Box A-12, Folder 137)
    - Black Heritage Dancers (Box A-12, Folder 138)
      Photographer if identified: Art Phipps
    - Black History (Box A-12, Folder 139)
      Photographer if identified: Allen Morgan,George Cohen, Bill Moore, Thomas Victor, Brown Brothers, Harris Photo
    - Black History Underground Railroad Game (Box A-12, Folder 140)
    - "Black Joy" (Box A-12, Folder 141)
    - Black, Holice Paul (Box A-12, Folder 142)
    - Black, Hugo L. Justice (Box A-12, Folder 143)
    - Black, Ivan See: Anna Lucasta (Box A-12, Folder 144)
    - Black Ivory (Box A-12, Folder 145)
    - Black Jews (Box A-12, Folder 146)
      Newspaper clippings, press releases, typescript news articles, photocopied telegrams, fax transmission to Kurt Waldheim. 2 prints have staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Lloyd Yearwood, Raymond H. Boone, Harris Photo, Bob Head, Wide World Photos
    - Black, Jim (Box A-12, Folder 147)
    - Black, Joe (Box A-12, Folder 148)
      Also a typescript article by Joe Black and one velox print.
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne, Markow Photography, Earl Fowler, Fabian Bachrach, Photography Unlimited, Harris Photo, James Gilbert, Howard Earl Day,
    - "Black Ice" (Box A-12, Folder 149)
    - Black Journal (Box A-12, Folder 150)
      Also one typescript press release (3 leaves).
    - Black Judges (Box A-12, Folder 151)
      1 print stapled to index card. Also a list of Federal judges in New York City.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Eric Hass, Kenneth R. Sanderson, Bill Mackey, Pictorial Enterprise, Yorkville Studio, King Photographers, YMCA of Greater New York, Conway Studios, Dick De Marsico, Tommy Comer, United Press International,
    - Black Judges (Box A-12, Folder 152)
      One print has a staple through the edge. One print is a Polaroid.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Denis Studio, Blackstone-Shelburne, A. Hansen, James Gilbert, Dave Greene, Gill Photographers, Ralph Cooper, King Photographers, Public Education Association, Studio of the New York Times,
    - Black, Kenneth (Box A-12, Folder 153)
      Photographer if identified: Don C. Hannover III
    - Black, Khendu (Box A-12, Folder 154)
    - Black Lawyers (Box A-12, Folder 155)
    - Black Leaders (Box A-12, Folder 156)
      Photographer if identified: Wagner International Photos, United Press International, King Photographers, James Gilbert,
    - Black, Lewis (Box A-12, Folder 157)
    - Black & Latino Caucus (Box A-12, Folder 158)
    - Black Liberation (Box A-12, Folder 159)
      Each print has several small mug shots.
    - Black Liberation Flag (Box A-12, Folder 160)
    - Black, Lucille (Box A-12, Folder 161)
    - "Black Like Me" (Box A-12, Folder 162)
    - Black Mayors (Box A-12, Folder 163)
    - 100 Black Men (Box A-12, Folder 164)
    - Black, Murray Dr. (on picture with Carroll, Edward W.) (Box A-12, Folder 165)
    - Black Music Assoc. & Musicians (Box A-12, Folder 166)
    - A Fashion Tribute to Black Music (Box A-12, Folder 167)
    - Black Muslim Rally See: Muslim Rally (Box A-12, Folder 168)
    - Black Nativity (Box A-12, Folder 169)
    - Black New World (Box A-12, Folder 170)
    - Miss Black New York (See M) (Box A-12, Folder 171)
    - Black News Digest (Box A-12, Folder 172)
      Typescript leaf stapled to recto of print.
    - Black Newspapers (Box A-12, Folder 173)
      2 velox prints.
    - "Black Olympics" (Box A-12, Folder 174)
    - Black Organizations (Box A-12, Folder 175)
      Photographer if identified: Ralph Cooper
    - Black Orpheus (Box A-12, Folder 178)
    - Black Orchid Florist (Box A-12, Folder 179)
    - Black Pearl Dancers (Box A-12, Folder 180)
    - Black Panther Party (Box A-12, Folder 181)
    - Black Pearl Private Car Service (Box A-12, Folder 182)
    - Black Photographers (Box A-12, Folder 183)
      Also invitation to Black Photographer's Annual.
      Photographer if identified: Lensman, Harris Photo, Nikki Grimes,
    - "Black Picture Show" (Box A-12, Folder 184)
    - Black Poets (Box A-12, Folder 185)
      Photographer if identified: Risasi-Zachariah Dais
    - Black Policemen See also: Policemen (Box A-12, Folder 186)
    - Black Politicians (Box A-12, Folder 187)
      Also one velox print. Two sets of prints in bags (approximately 6 and 2 prints, respectively) are stuck together with paste.
    - Black Politicians (Box A-12, Folder 188)
      Approximately 15 prints stuck together with paste in two bunches of approximately 13 and 2 prints, respectively. Also approximately 9 velox prints are stuck together with paste.
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo, Newell Johnson, Dave Greene, James Gilbert,
    - Black Politicians (Box A-12, Folder 189)
      5 prints mounted on mattes. Also a thank you letter from Judith-Ann Stewart. One print has a staple through the border.
      Photographer if identified: Paul Costin, James Gilbert, King Photographers, Harris Photo, Joe Williams, C. Tighlman,
      Number of Prints: 35
    - Black Politicians (Box A-12, Folder 190)
      Photographer if identified: David Greene, Pictorial Enterprise, Steve Goldstein
    - Black Politicians (Box A-13, Folder 1)
      Also 3 velox prints. One print has ms. leaf attached with staples through border. One print has typewritten leaf adhered to image. Also one clipping.
      Photographer if identified: Dave Greene, Peter G. Urba, Harris Photo, Gill Photographers, Norman Frederick, L. Benet McMillan, Pictorial Enterprise, News Voice International, King Photographers, Public Relations Office/NYC Parks Recreation and Cultural Affairs Administration
    - Black Politicians (Box A-13, Folder 2)
      Also six velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: Martin Bough, Blackstone Studios, Dave Greene, Pope's Studio, James Gilbert, Surgot School Color Photography
    - Black Power (Box A-13, Folder 3)
    - Black Press Week (Box A-13, Folder 4)
      Also one clipping and one board with multiple newspaper clippings and captions adhered
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Oggi's Kitchen
    - Black Princess (Box A-13, Folder 5)
      With typescript press release attached with paperclip.
    - Black Poetess (Box A-13, Folder 6)
    - Black and Puerto Rican Caucus Unity (Box A-13, Folder 7)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Newell Johnson, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Black Republicans (Box A-13, Folder 8)
    - Black, R.L. (Box A-13, Folder 9)
    - Black, Robert E. (Box A-13, Folder 10)
      Photographer if identified: Pope Photo
    - Black Rock Coalition (Box A-13, Folder 11)
    - Black Rose (Box A-13, Folder 12)
    - Black Rose (Box OS-1, Folder 2)
    - Black Scientists (Box A-13, Folder 13)
      Also two typescript leaves.
    - Black, Shirley Temple (Box A-13, Folder 14)
      One print with typescript leaf adhered to verso.
    - Black, Sidney S., Jr. (Box A-13, Folder 15)
    - Black Skiers (Box A-13, Folder 16)
    - Black Skin, White Mask (Box A-13, Folder 17)
      Photographer if identified: Erwin Doyle
    - Black Solidarity Day (Box A-13, Folder 18)
      One velox print. Also one press release.
      Photographer if identified: Lem Peterkin Photo, James Pozarik
    - Black Spectrum (Box A-13, Folder 19)
    - Black Speed Racers (Box A-13, Folder 20)
      Credited on press releases as "Black American RacersInc.." Some prints have typescript press releases attached with paperclips.
      Photographer if identified: Vincent Digaetano
    - Black Students (Box A-13, Folder 21)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Hamilton Associates
    - Miss Black Teenage (see (M)) (Box A-13, Folder 22)
    - Black Terror (Box A-13, Folder 23)
      Photographer if identified: Zodiac Photography
    - Black Theatre Alliance (Box A-13, Folder 24)
      With one typescript carbon press release adhered to the verso.
    - Black Theatre Workshop (Box A-13, Folder 25)